<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MusiceScape</string>
    <string name="fontName">MontserratBold.ttf</string>
    <string name="title_activity_app_info">   APP INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy">PrivacyActivity</string>
    <string name="splashScreen"> Music eScape was developed with young people by the Queensland University of Technology as part of the Young and Well Cooperative Research Centre\n\n We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining it.\n\n By continuing, you agree to music eScape\'s terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="privacy_statements">
       Music eScape was developed with young people aged 16-25 by the Queensland University of Technology (QUT) as part of a continuing research project in the Young and Well Cooperative Research Centre (Young and Well CRC) which is part of Young People, Technology and Wellbeing CRC Ltd. We are a not-for-profit organisation with objectives that include pursuing world class research and carrying out education for the benefit of Australians, especially young people. We focus on using technologies to promote mental health and wellbeing of young people. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining it.\n\n
        This Privacy Policy outlines how the Young and Well CRC collects and uses information online, and the safeguards we recommend to ensure a fun and safe experience. The applicable laws, being the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) as recently reformed (2014 March), and State and Territory privacy laws, establish Privacy Principles which have been adopted by us.\n\n
        To address your queries and ensure you are informed as you use this service:\n\n
        - You can use Music eScape without telling us who you are or revealing any information that personally identifies you (Personal Information).\n\n
        - The Young and Well CRC may use anonymous information on app usage (e.g., number of times used, duration of use, the pages visited inside the app) to ensure that the app continues to meet the needs of young people.\n\n
        - If you do provide us with any identifying information (e.g., your first name, email address or IP address) through your involvement in our research, we will deidentify the information prior to conducting the research. Personal information stored on servers is protected from modification, misuse, disclosure, loss and unauthorised access. Please note that we will not collect identifying information without your knowledge, and that this identifying information must be collected for your participation in this research.\n\n
        - You may ask us at any time to let you know what personal information we have collected from you. If you would like us to update or delete your personal information, please let us know and we will take all reasonable steps to delete it unless we are required by law to keep it.\n\n
        - No identifying information will be shared with third parties, within Australia or overseas. Non-identifying information (such as features of the songs in your library) will be shared with The Echo Nest, an international song database. This information needs to be sent for the app to work.\n\n
        - If you choose to share Music eScape through your social networks (via Facebook, Twitter or similar sites), you acknowledge that we do not manage or monitor those comments that may be made about this app on these channels.\n\n
        - Music eScape analyses your music by uploading a small proportion of each song to The Echo Nest, a music analysis database. This excludes the sharing of identifying information. By using Music eScape, you consent to this song information being sent from your iPhone.\n\n
        Young and Well CRC is not a mental health or crisis support service. Young people who need help should contact Kids Helpline, at http://www.kidshelp.com.au/ or 1800 55 1800; or Lifeline, at http://www.lifeline.org.au/ or 13 11 14. For more mental health services, visit us at http://www.youngandwellcrc.org.au/connect-with-us/support-services/.\n\n
        We may from time to time amend this Privacy Policy, and you may then choose to discontinue use of the service or continue usage subject to the revised Privacy Policy.\n\n
        If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please send an email to info@yawcrc.org.au.\n\n
        If you believe QUT has not dealt with your personal information in accordance with the Information Privacy Act or this policy, you may make a complaint to QUT. A complaint must be made in writing or by email to the Privacy Officer (privacy@qut.edu.au) or referred to that officer if received by another area of the University. The Privacy Officer will refer the matter to the head of the organisational unit to resolve the complaint.\n\n
        Primary responsibility for investigating and responding to the complaint will rest with the head of the organisational unit, with advice from the Privacy Officer as required. QUT’s main objective in responding to privacy complaints is to conciliate an outcome which is acceptable to the complainant and which addresses any broader or systemic privacy issues which may arise. If a complainant does not agree with the University\'s response, an internal review process is available or a complainant may refer the matter for independent mediation by the Office of the Information Commissioner.\n\n
         By using this app you acknowledge that this app is released for the purpose of research only.  This version is not released for commercial purposes and cannot be on-sold or distributed without the express written consent of Young and Well CRC Ltd. You as the user of the app acknowledge that you remain solely responsible for obtaining licensed content. You warrant that you will not use this app to create any infringing copies, support, encourage or induce copyright infringement. You indemnify and release the producer and authors of the app from any claim of intellectual property infringement arising from your music collection or your use of this app. If you are a copyright holder and have concerns regarding potential copyright infringement, please contact Young and Well CRC Ltd.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="dialog_msg">We\'ve finished tagging\n your library.\n\n Now all your songs will\n appear in playlist\n and mood journey</string>
    <string name="nt_dialog_msg">Looks like you\'re not on a\n network. \n Tospeed things up,and\n please enable your network</string>
    <string name="pref_previously_started">1</string>
    <string name="splash_msg">Takes you on a journey through emotions using your own music</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="pause">PAUSE</string>
    <string name="not_enough_draw_points">It looks like you haven\'t started drawing your mood journey or you don\'t have enough songs in your music library to create a mood journey.\\n\\n Try drawing again or adding more music to your library. \\n</string>
</resources>
